webtvonlive.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy – WebTV On Live

This page is used to inform ‘http://webtvonlive.com’ website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service, Web TV On Live.

If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at webtvonlive.com, unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web Browser Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.  
Our website uses these “cookies” to collection information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

**How we use collected information**

We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:  
To facilitate our Service;  
To provide the Service on our behalf;  
To perform Service-related services; or  
To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.  
We want to inform our Service users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

**How we protect your information**

We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Content**

We do not host any broadcasts on this website. All streams found on our site are found freely available around the web on sites such as Youtube.com, Ustream.tv, Livestream.com, Dailymotion.com, Dacast.com…  
We make no guarantees or promises in our service and take no liability for our users actions. We are not affiliated neither claim to be affiliated with any of the owners of broadcasts/streams played on our site.  
Whereas we do not filter such references, we cannot and do not attempt to control, censor, or block any material that may be considered offensive, defamatory, libelous, obnoxious, inaccurate, deceptive, unlawful or otherwise distressing neither do we accept responsibility for such content or the consequences of such content being made available.  
Material may be inappropriately described or subject to restrictions such as copyright, licensing and other limitations, and it is the responsibility of those having access to such material to comply with any and all lawful obligations arising from such material coming into their possession and thus mitigate any alleged transgression.  
Therefore, regarding access to content:  
All users warrant that they are 18 years of age or older, and therefore qualified to enter into this Agreement either as an individual or as a corporate entity.  
All users undertake to comply with the national laws applicable to the country in which they reside and observe the rights inherent in any copyright material whilst upholding the rights of any copyright owner.  
All users are advised to use caution, exercise discretion and use common sense and personal judgment when using this site or any references detailed within, and to respect the wishes of others who may value freedom from censorship as consenting adults equal to (or possibly superior to) your own personal preferences.

**Third-party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

WEB TV ON LIVE has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, you can send us an email directly:  
[webtvonlive@gmail.com](mailto:webtvonlive@gmail.com).
